The Legion is a adventure, history, action film directed by Jose Magan.
Noreno, a half-Roman, is entrusted with the mission of crossing the snowy mountains of
Armenia, swarming with Parthian patrols, to seek help for his slowly dying men.
Corbulo, played by Mickey Rourke.
Amirah, played by Bai Ling.
Paetus, played by Joaquim de Almeida.
Marcus, played by Vladimir Kulich.
Saul, played by Bosco Hogan.
The Legion is a 2020 Spanish-American action adventure film directed by
Jose Magan, and featuring Mickey Rourke and Bai Ling.
It is based on the war between Rome and Parthian
Empire in Armenia from 58 to 63 AD.
The Legion blends historical drama with action-adventure,
capturing a small but intense moment of ancient warfare.
However, the film has received mixed reviews for its pacing,
character development, and overall execution.
It is Magán's directorial debut.